<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nukleons Habits</string>
    <string name="use_fresh_food_title">Only fresh natural products</string>
    <string name="use_fresh_food_desc">Semi-finished products, packaged goods with a lot of preservatives, coloring agents, flavor enhancers do not fit into the system of healthy eating. After all, such food tremendously increases the load on the body, contributes to sluggish intestines, slows down metabolism and prevents the removal of toxins. So any piece of meat baked in the oven is healthier than store-bought sausage, even the best produced.</string>
    <string name="ogranich_raf_food_title">Limit refined foods</string>
    <string name="resume_desc">Eating too infrequently is just as harmful as eating too many snacks all the time. Try to have 3–4 meals a day, because a gap of more than 5 hours slows down the metabolism and sets the body to conserve energy. The consequence is the accumulation of fat deposits. You should not chew all the time either. Don\'t snack at the workplace, while watching TV or reading social media. So you do not control the process of food consumption, you do not feel satiated and cannot stop in time. As a result, you eat more than you need.</string>
    <string name="restrict_uglevod_title">Limit fast carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="restrict_uglevod_desc">Sugar from sweets and baked goods is quickly absorbed into the blood and immediately raises glucose levels. This is followed by an equally rapid drop in glucose, and you\'re hungry again. In addition, such rapid fluctuations in sugar have a negative effect on your body\'s performance.</string>
    <string name="carefull_salt_title">Careful with the salt</string>
    <string name="carefull_salt_desc">It is better to replace common table salt with sea salt or Himalayan salt. Cook\'s salt has only two trace elements - sodium and chlorine, while sea salt has up to 90 of them. And of course, you should try to gradually reduce your salt intake. We should not do away with salt altogether. But excess salt causes fluid retention in the body, leading to edema and high blood pressure.</string>
    <string name="drink_title">Drink water</string>
    <string name="drink_desc">Drink at least 30–35 milliliters of fluid per kilogram of your weight. Remember that coffee and juices are no substitute for water. By the way, it is better to give up juices and sweet fizzy drinks altogether - they contain too much sugar.</string>
    <string name="gotov_pish_title">Cook your food right</string>
    <string name="gotov_pish_desc">Minimal heat treatment is the key to preserving the integrity of foods. For example, you can boil cereal or pasta for just a few minutes. They are slightly stiff (al dente) and retain the healthy starch. For meat and fish, boiling, steaming, baking in the oven and (for a change!) grilling are the most suitable methods. And do not forget that sometimes it is not a crime to allow yourself a sausage sandwich or a cake. The main thing is that such a menu should not become a daily diet.</string>
    <string name="ogranich_raf_food_desc">The purified foods are deprived of such an important component as fiber, which is necessary for the work of the digestive organs, feeding the lacto- and bifidumbacteria that inhabit the intestinal walls. In practice, this means that instead of white loaf, it is better to eat wholemeal bread, and instead of white rice - brown rice. Ordinary refined sugar can be replaced by honey, agave syrup, topinambur or other natural sugars.</string>
    <string name="fresh_veg_food_title">Fruit and vegetables every day</string>
    <string name="fresh_veg_food_desc">Try to eat at least 300 grams of fresh vegetables and 300 grams of fresh fruit every day. With these foods you get soluble and insoluble fiber and essential vitamins. It is easiest to take an apple or pear cut into slices, carrot or celery sticks with you to work. In this way, you won\'t even notice how you eat the necessary amount of fruits and vegetables and satisfy your hunger at the same time.</string>
    <string name="belok_food_title">Stick to protein foods</string>
    <string name="belok_food_desc">First, it gives a long feeling of fullness. Secondly, it is rich in essential amino acids. Such foods include different kinds of meat, rabbit, guinea fowl, quail, fish and seafood, cod, perch, shrimp, squid, scallops, and others.</string>
    <string name="oil_title">A variety of vegetable oils</string>
    <string name="oil_desc">This is the best source of essential fatty acids (such as linoleic acid). It\'s a good idea to have four or five bottles of a variety of oils in your kitchen - linseed, grape seed, sesame, olive, walnut.</string>
    <string name="resume_title">Stick to the regimen</string>
</resources>